<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Class Scheduling System</string>
    <string name="ip_addr">http://172.19.13.70:8080/scheduleing/</string>
    <string name="about">Class Scheduler App is an Android application to facilitate the scheduling of classes within an academic institute.\n
        The instructors can easily schedule extra classes in the free slots and can cancel the already scheduled classes.\n
        The students are given a facility to vote for the class that has been proposed to be scheduled by the instructors. Based on the student votes, decisions of classes being scheduled or ignored are taken.
        The notifications are sent to the students and instructors about the upcoming classes before 2 hrs of the class time.
    </string>
    <string name="instructions_for_instructor">
        Color Coding:-\n
        pale yellow - scheduled classes\n
        green - classes in process of being scheduled\n
        blue - empty classes\n\n
        You can schedule a class on an empty slot. For doing so, simply click on the slot. A popup appears which asks for subject id of subject taught by you. Enter the info and click submit. Rest is done by the app. You will notice the changes.\n\n
        To cancel the fixed class, simply click on the slot (yellow colored) and select yes in the dialog that appears. Class will be canceled.\n\n
        To cancel the class that is in process of being scheduled (green colored) follow the same procedure as for fixed class.\n\n
        You can only cancel your own classes and can only schedule your own classes. Classes can not be scheduled during break time or on the fixed slots.\n\n
        Carefully read the notifications and information written on screen or popped to you via dialog, toasts and snackbars.

    </string>
    <string name="instructions_for_student">
        Color Coding:-\n
        Same as instructors\n\n
        You can only vote on the classes that are in process of being scheduled (green colored).\n\n
        You can vote once per green colored slot, so choose you vote wisely.\n\n
        To vote, click on the slot and select yes or no as your vote when dialog appears.\n\n
        Carefully read the notifications and information written on screen or popped to you via dialog, toasts and snackbars.
    </string>
</resources>
